二零二一年上海市初中学业水平考试英语第一部分听力部分即将开始。
这里是上海人民广播电台
of the first the the first part part of the first part part part part
长三角之声，
八十九点九，
七九二。
这里是上海人民广播电台长三角之声，
八十九点九，
七九二。
二零二一年上海市初中学业水平考试英语第一部分听力部分即将开始。
现在先试音。
试音的内容是一段音乐，请注意调节音量和音调。
下面，请听音乐。
试音到此结束，听力部分现在开始。
根据你听到的内容，选出相应的图片，并在答题纸上填涂相应的字母代号
每个句子念两遍。
of the first part part of the part first part of first part first
根据你听到的对话和问题，选出最恰当的答案，并在答题纸上填涂相应的
字母代号。
对话和问题都念。
part part of the part
first part part of the first part of the first the
first the first part of the part part
first part part first part of the first part of the first part of the first part
first part first part part
再听一遍.
of the first part first part
of part part part part of the
判断句子是否符合你听到的对话内容，符合的用
表示，不符合的用
表示。
并在答题纸上填涂相应的字母代号。
对话念两遍：
first part first part of the first part of the first part of the
first part first part of the
first part of the first part of the first part of the
first part of the first part of
first part part of the
first part of the first part of the
first part of the first part of the first part of the first part of the first part
听短文，用听到的单词。
part part first part of part
first part of first part part part of the part part of the
first part of the first the part of the
first part part of the first part part part of the
first part of first part of the part of the first part of the first part
听力部分到此结束。
first part of the the